Hi, I'm Richie Pandey.
嗨我是里奇 - 潘迪
I'm Richer Cahal.
我是瑞奇 - 卡哈尔
I'm Vienna Harvey.
我是维也纳哈维
I'm Brian Okaykay and I'm a Curriculum Manager and self-taught full-stack developer.
我是 Brian Okaykay  我是课程经理 也是自学的全栈开发者
I'm manager at self-driving car here at Udacity.
我是 Udacity的自驾车经理
I'm a content creator and software engineer.
我是一个内容创造者和软件工程师
Here at Udacity, I've been developing programs in data science.
在 Udacity  我一直在开发数据科学的项目
Let's discuss strategies for learning new technical skills.
让我们讨论学习新技术技能的策略
Learning a new skill can be really exciting but can also be
学习一门新技能可以让人兴奋 但也可以
challenging especially in a self-paced online program.
尤其是在一个自定进度的网上节目中
We start by defining a learning path so that we know
我们从定义学习路径开始 以便我们知道
what our goals are and that we're making progress towards them.
我们的目标是什么 ?
A goal can mean to finish a particular course,
一个目标可以完成一个特定的课程
or complete a nano degree program and get a new job.
或者完成一个纳米级的程序 得到一个新的工作
Maybe you're just personally curious about
也许你只是好奇
a topic and want to broaden your knowledge base.
一个话题 想拓宽你的知识基础
Whatever your goal is,
不管你的目标是什么
try to keep it in mind.
尽量保持理智
It shapes how you learn.
它塑造了你学习的方式
When it comes to goals,
说到目标
one strategy is to set short term goals and long-term goals.
一个策略就是设定短期目标和长期目标
If your goal is to complete a project or apply to a certain kind of job,
如果你的目标是完成一个项目或者申请某种工作
then you should write an incremental plan to get there.
那你应该写个递增计划去那里
Knowing specific steps to take or milestones to
了解要执行的特定步骤或里程碑
reach can help you stay on track and not feel overwhelmed.
可以帮助您继续跟踪 而不是感到不知所措
Take each step as you achieve it so you
当你实现它的每一步
can see yourself moving closer to your long-term goals.
可以看到自己更接近你的长远目标
Keeping yourself accountable to a goal is really important.
让自己对一个目标负责是很重要的
Serious, so important.
真的很重要
Set calendar reminders for yourself to keep yourself
为自己设置日历提醒 以保持自己
accountable and learn some small thing every day.
每天都要负责和学习一些小事
Try to add an additional layer of
尝试添加附加层
accountability by telling a partner or a friend about it,
向合伙人或朋友交代
or even your coworker, or boss.
甚至是你的同事或者老板
Someone you can check on your progress.
您可以查看您的进度
Enroll in a program with a buddy to help you stay committed to completing the program.
与伙伴一起加入一个计划 帮助您继续致力于完成该计划
Studies show it takes time to form a new habit.
研究表明 形成一种新习惯需要时间
So get into the habit of working on your program.
所以养成在你的节目中工作的习惯
Once learning becomes a habit,
一旦学习成为习惯
it won't take so much effort to sit down and work on you program.
它不会花那么多力气坐下来给你工作
When you feel like procrastinating,
当你觉得拖延的时候
remind yourself why you enrolled in the program in the first place.
提醒自己你当初为什么要参加这个节目
To help motivate you.
为了帮助激励你
Then, reward yourself when you stick with the habit
那就当你养成习惯的时候
I like to get myself an ice cream cone.
我喜欢吃冰淇淋
Having a plan and checking off smaller items makes
制定计划并对较小的项目进行检查
the larger task of learning a whole new skill seem a bit more approachable.
学习整个新技能的更大的任务似乎更接近了
You can even set a goal of finishing one exercise or part of the lesson in one sitting.
你甚至可以在一次会议上设定完成一个练习或部分课程的目标
The Udacity classroom has projects and
Udacity 教室有项目
suggested project deadlines that you can use as well.
建议您也可以使用的项目截止期限
While these projects are good milestones,
虽然这些项目是很好的里程碑
more importantly they provide
更重要的是
hands-on learning to actively practice the skills that you've got.
动手学习 积极练习你所掌握的技能
Now, these projects are meant to be challenging.
现在 这些项目注定要充满挑战
I know it can be frustrating to get stuck in
我知道被困在
the middle of a project that is really difficult.
一个非常困难的项目的中间
Ooh.
我的天啊
Oh God.
天啊
Ooh.
我的天啊
But those times are often the ones where there's
但那些时间往往是
more room for exploration and innovation.
更多的探索和创新的空间
For example, when writing a new function,
例如 写新函数时
explain the function in simple sentences or pseudo-code,
用简单的句子或伪码解释函数
and only then move on to writing the syntax.
然后才开始写语法
Build on things incrementally.
以增量方式构建事物
Everyone struggles with it when they learn something new.
当他们学习新事物时 每个人都与之斗争
Be patient with yourself.
耐心耐心
For example, software programmers in the industry have
例如 业界的软件程序员有
in several years to become masters in their domain.
在几年里成为他们的主人
To remind yourself of your goal,
为了提醒自己你的目标
remember every step is getting you closer to it.
记住每一步都让你更接近它
Now, when working with code,
现在 当使用代码时
there are a lot of great resources for when you hit a roadblock.
当你撞上路障的时候会有很多大的资源
Making mistakes in your code is actually a great way to learn.
在你的代码中犯错其实是一个学习的好方法
A lot of my on code projects are developed one error at a time.
很多我的代码项目一次出现一个错误
One habit and skill good programmers have is to read
一个习惯和技能优秀的程序员要阅读
error messages and practice figuring out what exactly is not working in the code.
错误消息和实践 确定代码中不工作的内容
Being able to use resources to fix
能够使用资源来修复
your code is a problem solving skills in and of itself.
你的密码是解决问题的方法
Community-led sites like Stack Overflow or Udacity's own tool called Knowledge,
" Stack Overflow " 或 " Udacity " 自己的名为 " 知识" 的工具
where people answer each other's questions can be very useful.
人们回答对方的问题会非常有用
One of the best ways is just to
最好的方法之一就是
type in an error message into Google and see what comes up.
将错误消息输入 Google 并查看出现的内容
Because someone else has probably had the same error and maybe figured out a solution.
因为别人可能有同样的错误 也许想出了一个解决办法
Also read blog posts and source code to
也阅读博客帖子和源代码到
see how someone else is thinking through a similar problem.
看看别人怎么想过类似的问题
Technical concepts can be hard to learn and
技术概念可能难以学习和
it's normal to get an imperfect solution after the first trial.
在第一次审判后得到不完美的解决方案是正常的
It's highly recommended to start with something that is small,
强烈建议从很小的东西开始
that works and incrementally improve it.
并且不断地改进它
Okay. Let's summarize.
好吧好吧 总结一下
Set goals for yourself and hold yourself
为自己设定目标并保持自己
accountable with a schedule or an accountability buddy.
负责调度或问责伙伴
Breakdown projects into small goals.
将项目分解为小目标
Work on incremental parts of the lesson.
对课程的增量部分进行工作
Work, do exercises to make the learning stick.
工作 做练习 做学习棒
Start with pseudo-code and use practice and online resources.
以伪代码和使用实践和联机资源开始
You've got this. So good luck.
你有这个 祝你好运
Happy learning.
快乐学习